NWAY AUNG IT EXECUTIVE/ IT SUPPORT



Contact

Address: 199 Lasalle Rd, Bang Na Tai, Bang Na, Bangkok 10260

WhatsApp: +66649186741

Email: nwayaungtkpn@gmail.com

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/nway-aung-2b22b9147

Summary and Statement

As an experienced IT Technician with over 5 years of expertise, I have a proven track record of providing technical support and troubleshooting to ensure smooth operations. I have successfully contributed to various organizations, including Kinetic Co., Ltd., Myanmar Net Co., Ltd., and M.Y Industrial Ingredients Co., Ltd. My skill set includes implementing network infrastructure, systems administration, cloud computing architecture, Office 365 administration, information system support and security, and network and server support.

EDUCATION

(2011-2016)

UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (YADANARPON CYBER CITY)
B.E (Electronics and Communication)

Certifications

- AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate
- Linux Challenges (KodeKloud)
- Microsoft Azure Fundamental

PROJECT EXPERIENCES

- CCTV Installation and Network Design and cabling.
- ADDS, DNS, DHCP, Windows Server installation and Configuration.
- Implementation of Synology Backup System
- Microsoft Server Migration Project

EXPERIENCE WITH

- Windows Server
 Installation
- Active Directory
- Advanced File Sharing
- DHCP and DNS Management
- GPO

- MikroTik VPN, Load
 Balancing
- Peachtree Accounting
 Service
- Cloud Fundamental (AWS, Digital Ocean)
- CCTV (IP and Analog)
 Installation

- Email Service (G-Suite, M365)
- Microsoft 365 Administrator
- Virtualization (Hyper-V and VMware)
- Synology NAS and File Server

SOFT SKILLS

- Capable of working both independently and collaboratively within a team.
- Strong communication and excellent organizational skills.
- Skilled in quickly establishing good working relationships with clients and vendors.
- Proficient in verbal and written communication, with the ability to explain technical issues to non-technical users.

EXPERIENCES

M.Y INDUSTRIAL INGREDIENTS CO., LTD

IT Support (February 2020 — Present)

- Manage and maintain computer systems, networks and server, install and configure hardware and software components.
- Deliver timely and effective technical support to end-users, resolving issues and minimizing downtime.
- Configure and optimize Windows Server Applications such as DNS, DHCP, and File and Storage services.
- Manage and maintain network infrastructure, ensuring the smooth operation of IT systems.
- Install, configure and maintain Microsoft365 Services such as Exchange, Team and Sharepoint.
- Recommends hardware and software solutions, including new acquisitions and upgrades
- Setup group policies on Local Server and GPO

Lan Operation Engineer (September 2018 — December 2020)

- Managed and maintained local area networks, ensuring high-speed and reliable connectivity
- Installation and troubleshooting CPE devices, routers and switches
- Managed CPEs, routers and switches in remote
- Solved customer complain for any network problem
- Participated in efforts that develop recommendations and advice on system development, improvements and optimization
- Performed as a senior technical participant with knowledge and experience in local and wide area networking, communications, and related software/hardware within a multi-platform operating environment
- Supported overall technical delivery for the client

KINETIC CO., LTD

Fiber Engineer (February 2017 — June 2018)

- Installed and configured fiber optic cables and equipment.
- Performed regular maintenance and troubleshooting to detect and resolve fiber issues.
- Collaborated with team members to ensure the timely completion of projects.
- Conducted tests and measurements to ensure the quality and performance of fiber optic networks.
- Responsible for planning, survey and execution of client sites on fiber
- Fiber Blowing, splicing and termination of fiber cables